<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Wasteland</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Software Wasteland</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:12:28 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sourcing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/sourcing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:12:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/sourcing/</guid>
      <description>Where to find candidates In many ways I think of this as starting from the inside out. The things that you have the most control over are the people in your network and the relationships you&amp;rsquo;ve already built with them. You can then begin to work your way outside to other sources
Referrals are best Brainstorm the 5 best engineers in your network that would fit the job description. Setup a lunch / call with them and check in on them, ask them who the 5 best engineers they know are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phone Screen</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/phone-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:03:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/phone-screen/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this call is to identify any show stoppers that the candidate might be hiding.
Note: This does not need to be completed by engineers.
Timing Showstoppers Where are you at in your job search? This gives you a good idea of where they are at, how fast to move, how sophisticated they are at interviewing When could you start? This is a simple but effective question to understand if they have been fired, quit, or if they are just looking around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 16:33:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/hiring/</guid>
      <description>Steps Job Description (Bait) Sourcing Resume Review Phone Screen Technical Screen Job Description A job description is critical to finding the write candidate.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to highlight aspects of the job that are critical. Make sure things like REMOTE are higlighted. Get the Job Title right. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to put the level of engineer you are looking for different people will respond to a Principal Engineer than a Senior Engineer Look at some of the best in class recruiting companies for reference, but remember to make it your own User test your job description.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
